♪ AH LOOK AT ALL THE
LONELY PEOPLE ♪
♪ ELEANOR RIGBY, PICKS UP
THE RICE ♪
♪ IN THE CHURCH WHERE A
WEDDING HAS BEEN ♪
♪ LIVES IN A DREAM ♪
♪ WAITS AT THE WINDOW,
WEARING THE FACE ♪
♪ THAT SHE KEEPS IN A JAR BY
THE DOOR ♪
♪ WHO IS IT FOR ♪
♪ ALL THE LONELY PEOPLE ♪
♪ WHERE DO THEY ALL COME FROM? ♪
♪ WHERE DO THEY ALL BELONG? ♪
♪ FATHER MCKENZIE, WRITING
THE WORDS ♪
♪ OF A SERMON THAT NO ONE
WILL HEAR ♪
♪ NO ONE COMES NEAR ♪
♪ LOOK AT HIM WORKING, DARNING
HIS SOCKS ♪
♪ IN THE NIGHT WHEN THERE'S
NOBODY THERE ♪
♪ WHAT DOES HE CARE ♪
♪ ALL THE LONELY PEOPLE ♪
♪ WHERE DO THEY ALL COME FROM? ♪
♪ WHERE DO THEY ALL BELONG? ♪
♪ AH LOOK AT ALL THE
LONELY PEOPLE ♪
♪ ELEANOR RIGBY, DIED IN
THE CHURCH ♪
♪ AND WAS BURIED ALONG WITH
HER NAME ♪
♪ NOBODY CAME ♪
♪ FATHER MCKENZIE, WIPING
THE DIRT ♪
♪ FROM HIS HANDS AS HE WALKS
FROM THE GRAVE ♪
♪ NO ONE WAS SAVED ♪
♪ ALL THE LONELY PEOPLE ♪
♪ WHERE DO THEY ALL COME FROM? ♪
♪ WHERE DO THEY ALL BELONG? ♪
♪ ♪